up let's head to VI for all the movs and
shakers VI well thank you so much for
that you know like you mentioned today
you know one pack that actually
outperformed was the tech Pac and Tech
Pac you know given the fact that TCS has
one of the highest weightages as far as
the entire it index is concerned Ended
as one of the top gainers as in within
the Nifty so TCS you know on the back of
the upgrade from UBS that came in that
particular stock ended Higher by over 2
and a half% the second stock one that
we'll be discussing further too is IC
Lombard so IC Bank further Paris take
and the overhang of bti Enterprises take
sale is likely now over as well the
third stock you know again on the back
of a brokerage upgrade was hav India now
this particular stock you know continued
to up ended Higher by almost 3% higher
and you know Goldman Sachs continues to
remain quite positive as far as hav is
concern the fourth stock cell world you
know something we discussed in the
morning moal initiated coverage they
believe that this stock has significant
potential and the Target price of 1100
is what they've ascribed to sell World
stock ended High over 4% and within the
gaining pack the last stock was happiest
mind the announcement came during the
middle of Aras the company is going
ahead and reorganizing the entire
vertical structure and on the back of
that the stock ended High about over 4
and a half% but quite a few stocks saw
selling pressure as well the first stock
of course was Dixon you actually saw
downgrade coming in from Jeff's over
stretched valuations as well as post you
know very sharp runup they went ahead
and downgraded the stock the second
stock you know that will be on
everybody's mind is Vodafone idea today
you know just ahead of the board meet
the stock ended low quite significant L
but all eyes on this particular name you
know as the outcome of the fundraising
board meet is upon us and lastly sham
Finance very very volatile stock in
today's trading session ended Low by
over 4 and a half% remember now this
particular stock is a candidate to go
ahead and replace UPL once you know the
Nifty Nifty reig you know actually comes
into effect so lot of volatility over
there but we remain and we need to see
if there is any Clarity that emerges
especially if NS go ahead and decides to
include the stock in the nifty 50 index
okay all right got that VI thank you
very much for all of that action Let's
uh now